https://www.duraskirt.com/privacy-statement/

CoronavirusHomeAbout UsPrivacy StatementContact UsDURASKIRT™ DownloadsDURASKIRT™ BrochureDURASKIRT™ EngineeringDURASKIRT™ PRE-ORDER FORMDURASKIRT™ Pricing by Home SizesDURASKIRT™ SDS SHEETDURASKIRT™ TERMITE RESISTANCE LETTERDURASKIRT™ WarrantyHIDDEN-VENT CALCULATIORInstallation Detail DrawingsInstallation ManualDURASKIRT™ InformationDURASKIRT™ Kit PricingDURASKIRT™ Mobile Home Skirting Order FormConcrete Skirting – How Does DURASKIRT™ Compare?DURASKIRT™ Concrete Board and Exterior Cement BoardTrailer Skirting & Underpinning“Hidden-Vent”Mobile Home Skirting Installation VideosPhotosTestimonialsOther ProductsPrecast Concrete Wheel StopsRetrofit Cart by DURASKIRT™Parking Lot Bollards | Precast barriers | Mount Vernon, Washington“The Green Box”FAQSBlogHouse Skirting IdeasCheap Mobile Home SkirtingShed SkirtingPrivacy Statement Home
Privacy StatementPrivacy Statement for MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC for the following websites:Duraskirt.com | Duraskirt.org | Duraskirt.info |GreenGardenBox.com| MHServiceandSupply.comMH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy when you use our online, telephone or other services (“Services”). In this policy we explain how and why we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it. From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products to our Web Site or add or change Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments. Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC at info@duraskirt.com or alternatively see the section “Comments” below. Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms by using Duraskirt.com, Duraskirt.info, Duraskirt.org, MHServiceandSupply.com or GreenGardenBox.com (“Web Sites”) or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.What data do we collect and how do we use it?MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC collects and processes information about you in order to: (i) identify you each time you visit our Web Site or wish to have a Service provided; (ii) process orders or applications submitted by you; (iii) improve our Services and Web Site (iv) Customize your experience; (v) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behavior of all of our customers; and (vi) send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC products and services. You may be asked, either when you register with us, or at other times, for information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from our Web Site, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date. You are under no obligation to provide this information, but if you don’t then we may not be able to provide you with certain services or personalize your experience and tailor our Services for you (for example, tell you about special offers on things you’re interested in). Duraskirt.com | Duraskirt.org Duraskirt.info | GreenGardenBox.com | MHServiceandSupply.comPrivacy StatementLog files/IP addresses When you visit our Web Site, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Site and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.Non-personal information we may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you entered our Web Site. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our Web Site.Use of Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. If you select to block cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web Site. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the Internet. While cookies do identify a user’s computer, they do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.We use cookies for the following reasons:To recognize your computer and to access your account information; To estimate our audience size and patterns; To ensure that you are not asked to register twice; To track preferences and to improve and update our Web Site; and To track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests. With whom is the information shared?MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf. Duraskirt.com | Duraskirt.org | Duraskirt.info | GreenGardenBox.com | MHServiceandSupply.com.MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our Web Site visitors and customers of our telephone services in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC and its Web Sites, visitors to the Web Sites and customers of our Services. Our Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites. We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a sale of the assets of MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.Information about products and services It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In order to help us do this, from time to time MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC may send you details of our products and services which we think may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive these details, please e-mail us at info@duraskirt.com.SecurityMH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC places great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized personnel have access to user information. Regarding our Web Site we use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.Where is the information stored? Information which you submit via our Web Site or our telephone services is stored on a computer located at our headquarters in Mount Vernon, WA. This is necessary in order to Duraskirt.com | Duraskirt.org | Duraskirt.info | GreenGardenBox.com | MHServiceandSupply.com to process the information and to send you any information you have requested. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to reputable third-party suppliers, which may be situated outside the United States. Not all countries outside the U.S. have data protection or privacy laws. In addition, if you use our Services while you are outside the U.S., your information may be transferred outside the U.S. in order to provide you with those Services.CommentsPlease e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy Policy to info@duraskirt.com or write to us at: MH SERVICE & SUPPLY, LLC 115 Lind Street, Mount Vernon, WA 98273 | 1-360-419-9909 Rate this page Contact UsWe're not around right now. But you can send us an email and we'll get back to you, asap.
Send Message
DURASKIRT™ Premium Concrete Mobile Home Skirting and Underpinning For Manufactured Homes Get Prices!© 2020 — Creative Concrete Products, LLCCoronavirusHomeAbout UsPrivacy StatementContact UsDURASKIRT™ DownloadsDURASKIRT™ BrochureDURASKIRT™ EngineeringDURASKIRT™ PRE-ORDER FORMDURASKIRT™ Pricing by Home SizesDURASKIRT™ SDS SHEETDURASKIRT™ TERMITE RESISTANCE LETTERDURASKIRT™ WarrantyHIDDEN-VENT CALCULATIORInstallation Detail DrawingsInstallation ManualDURASKIRT™ InformationDURASKIRT™ Kit PricingDURASKIRT™ Mobile Home Skirting Order FormConcrete Skirting – How Does DURASKIRT™ Compare?DURASKIRT™ Concrete Board and Exterior Cement BoardTrailer Skirting & Underpinning“Hidden-Vent”Mobile Home Skirting Installation VideosPhotosTestimonialsOther ProductsPrecast Concrete Wheel StopsRetrofit Cart by DURASKIRT™Parking Lot Bollards | Precast barriers | Mount Vernon, Washington“The Green Box”FAQSBlogHouse Skirting IdeasCheap Mobile Home SkirtingShed Skirting Type and press Enter to search
We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings. Accept
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful. Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again. Enable All Save Settings
